<?xml version="1.0"?>
<quotes_list>
	<quote id="0">
		<author>Jean Paul</author>
		<body>No rest is worth anything except the rest that is earned.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="1">
		<author>Bruce Lee</author>
		<body>If you always put limits on everything you do, physical or anything else, it will spread into your work and into your life. There are no limits. There are only plateaus, and you must not stay there, you must go beyond them.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="2">
		<author>Thomas Edison</author>
		<body>Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="3">
		<author>Confucius</author>
		<body>The will to win, the desire to succeed, the urge to reach your full potential... these are the keys that will unlock the door to personal excellence.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="4">
		<author>Jim Valvano</author>
		<body>Never give up! Failure and rejection are only the first step to succeeding.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="5">
		<author>Anonymous</author>
		<body>Keep your goals out of reach, but not out of sight.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="6">
		<author>Mike Ditka</author>
		<body>Before you can win, you have to believe you are worthy.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="7">
		<author>Anonymous</author>
		<body>Success comes before work... only in the dictionary.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="8">
		<author>Steve Michalik</author>
		<body>Train beyond the pain..and death is your only release</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="9">
		<author>Guy Cisternino</author>
		<body>To anyone that ever tells you that you can't do something - tell them to go f*** themselves.</body>
	</quote>
    <quote id="10">
		<author>Robert Louis Stevenson</author>
		<body>Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.</body>
	</quote>    
    <quote id="11">
        <author>Buddha</author>
        <body>Health is the greatest gift, contentment the greatest wealth, faithfulness the best relationship.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="12">
        <author>Nido Qubein</author>
        <body>Your present circumstances don't determine where you can go; they merely determine where you start.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="13">
        <author>Michael Jordan</author>
        <body>If you accept the expectations of others, especially negative ones, then you never will change the outcome.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="14">
        <author>Hagrid</author>
        <body>You're a Wizard, Harry</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="15">
        <author>Yoda</author>
        <body>Do, or do not. There is no "try".</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="16">
        <author>President Merkin Muffley</author>
        <body>Gentlemen, you can't fight in here! This is the War Room.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="17">
        <author>Darth Vader</author>
        <body>Luke, I am your father.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="18">
        <author>Mitch Hedberg</author>
        <body>My fake plants died because I did not pretend to water them.</body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="19">
        <author>Sun Tzu</author>
        <body>Appear weak when you are strong, and strong when you are weak. </body>
    </quote>
    <quote id="20">
        <author>Voltaire</author>
        <body>The art of medicine consists in amusing the patient while nature cures the disease.</body>
    </quote>
    
</quotes_list>